Original Work
Story
Character Design
Original Work
Story
Character Design
Akira Toriyama
(Shueisha "Jump Comics”)
Hee, hee, hee!
Uhhyohyo!
Time to adventure! I'm gettin' hooked for sure!
Bouken suzzo! Zettee hamaru zo!
Planning
Akio Iyoku
Kōzō Morishita
Atsushi Suzuki
It's the Demon Realm, full of mystery
Nazo darake no Makai da
Executive Producers
Kei Naitō
Hiroki Koyama
Producers
Taku Hirokawa
Mamoru Kunihiro
A DAIMA Wonderland
Series Composition / Screenplay
Yūko Kakihara
Whoopsie daisy!
Ottotto!
Even on the days my heart shrinks and I'm feelin' low
Haato chijinde choushi denai hi mo
Theme Music Producer
Music
Kōsuke Yamashita
I've got dozens of dreams, and no need to worry
Yume wa TORI-dori Na-YAMA-nai
Opening Theme Song
"Jaka ☆ Jaan"
Composition:
Lyrics:
Yukinojō Mori
Artists:
I won't give up
AKIRA-menai
Cooperation
Shueisha
V-Jump / Saikyou Jump Editorial Depts.
Dragon Ball Room
Here comes a New Story
Production Managers
Takeshi Sawamori
Yūki Atsumi
Art Director
Maya Kasai
Color Design
Rumiko Nagai
CG Director
Yoshitaka Ikegami
Director of Photography
Naoyuki Wada
Thousands of jabs and weird gags
Nanzen no jabu ga hen na gyagu ga
Prop Design
Hidemitsu Masui
Art Design
Maya Kasai
Takashi Kurahashi
are waitin' for me
Matteirunda
Jaan! Jaka ☆ jaan
Sound the fanfare of courage (Jaan! Jaka ☆ jaan)
Saa yuuki fanfaare (Jaan! Jaka ☆ jaan)
All-out, crazy battles... My excitement ain't stoppin'
Zenkai yabee batoru wakuwaku ga tomaranai
Hey, Shenlong... Grant my wish (my wish)
Nee Shenlong... Negai kanaete (kanaete)
Animation Character Design,
Chief Animation Director
Katsuyoshi Nakatsuru
Series Director
Aya Komaki
Yoshitaka Yashima
I wanna meet someone amazin' again tomorrow
Ashita mo suggee yatsu ni aitai
Produced by
Toei Animation
My plane…
They couldn't have...
Huh?
CHATTY
Blast it. I know I locked it.
What now?
Will we be able to return to Earth?
I'll figure out something.
Let's keep walking and find a vehicle.
It'll be easy if we just fly.
You can all fly, right?
Long distances are difficult in this air.
It expends a lot of energy
and will tire you out quickly.
Huh...
Hup!
Huh?
Yeah, it's heavy.
So the air's heavy. I get it.
Depleting our stamina traveling
would be dangerous.
Let's walk.
Oh? It's a dead end.
What do we do?
Let's fly here.
Hup! Whoops!
I guess you need to fly to get anywhere
in the Demon World, huh?
We could get around easily
if we only had my plane.
Falling into the Sea of Darkness
would be bad, so let's be careful.
Goku-san, your movements
aren't as sharp as they usually are.
I still ain't used to the air yet.
What is this place?
You can't let your guard down, can you?
I'll deal with it.
Begone.
Wow, you ain't bad at all!
You might even be stronger
than Kaioshin-sama.
I'm a pretty good fighter myself, though.
Let's keep going.
I'm so hungry.
Try to hold out until the next town.
Ain't there any good fruits or anythin'?
Huh? Someone's hidin' for an ambush again.
Man, my body feels heavy.
Whew, that was tiring.
How did you know it was there?
I didn't see anything.
Right. Its Ki.
I just sensed its Ki.
Ki?
What is that?
An invisible sort of energy one can sense.
Hm? There's somethin' there.
nI-evirD
It looks like a shop.
Let's take a break there.
At last! I can eat!
I'm starvin'!
Boo!
Sorry for the wait. Here's your tea.
And this is our highly recommended dish!
That smells delish!
It's skewered lizard.
Time to eat!
This is good!
What's this?
Herb juice with honey.
We're famous for it. It's delicious!
Bitter!
That flavor really grows on you.
It's full of nutrition!
The healthiest drink in the world!
Glorio-san. You said we'd find
another vehicle somewhere.
Do you have an idea where?
Well…
Honey, you're needed!
What is it?
Do you have a plane?
What?
We're looking for a plane.
Hmm…
What was that?
Honey! They need a plane! A plane!
Right.
I haven't got anything that valuable,
but I can sell you a Sky Seed for 8,000.
A Sky Seed…
What's the distance?
Hm?
He's asking the distance!
Ah, right, right.
For you and two kids,
probably around 120 kilometers.
120 kilometers… For 8,000 Dokuro…
That's a little pricey.
I guess I'll try elsewhere.
I-I'll take 5,000! How's that?!
There's a lot of weird stuff.
I wonder what this is?
Maybe a piece of candy?
Ah, it's a dead bug. What's it doin' here?
A bug?!
You boys aren't from around here, are you?
That's a Revive Bug.
It's a kind of Medi Bug
that'll restore stamina if you eat it.
Huh. That's cool.
So it's like a Senzu.
What are you talking about?
There seem to be a lot of different bugs.
Yes. We've got most of the different types
of Medi Bugs you can find around here.
Achichi Bugs for burns,
Zutsu Bugs for headaches,
Beaut Bugs to make your skin silky smooth.
What's this bug?
¡¡GNORTS emoceB DnA eGreM
guB nioj
That's a Join Bug.
¡¡GNORTS emoceB DnA eGreM
guB nioj
Feed halves to two people
¡¡GNORTS emoceB DnA eGreM
guB nioj
and they can merge for a while,
making them stronger.
Wow! It's like Fusion!
Hey, Goliro!
It's Glorio.
What is it?
Buy a few of these bugs here for me!
Bugs?
Ah, Medi Bugs.
Really?! How very nice!
We haven't sold souvenirs
here for decades!
Thanks a lot, Goliro!
It's Glorio.
Hey. This way.
Wait here.
gnidraoB deeS ykS
ereH
"Sky Seed boarding here"?
gnidraoB deeS ykS
ereH
What's that?
gnidraoB deeS ykS
ereH
I've never heard of that before either.
Step right up! Sorry for the wait!
A dream flight for you and me
for a love-filled night!
The ever-popular Sky Seed
boarding is right here!
Looks kinda interestin'!
Here we go! Three to go, right?!
The Sky Seed will be here momentarily!
Wait right where you are!
What kind of amazin' ride is it?!
What is that?
A seed of a Great Fiend Flower
called a Sky Seed.
It's not quite what I imagined.
There we go.
So, where are you headed?
That direction.
Sure thing.
Okay!
Right!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Your destination is up to you!
Now step right up
and take a seat, my friends!
Like this?
I wonder how it moves.
You boys hold onto the gentleman in front!
Keep your heads down!
I'm removing the tail now,
so hold on tight!
Five… Four… Three…
Two… One…
Liftoff!
Take care!
- We're going so fast!
- Hold on tight!
Whoa! This feels great!
It is rather nice.
Glorio-san, how are you driving this?
I'm not.
Huh?
The seed is just flying.
Wait a minute…
Does that mean we're going to fall?!
That's right. So we need to
get off before it crashes.
What?!
We're starting to descend!
Fall in the Sea of Darkness
and you'll be done for! Be careful!
Got it!
Now! Get away!
Whoa.
It looks like we covered a lot of ground.
How much farther is the castle?
We should arrive after half a day's walk.
Half a day, huh?
Let's fly the rest of the way.
If we run out of stamina, we can eat
some of those Revive Bugs we bought earlier.
I don't really like bugs...
Same here.
Man, I'm thirsty.
Come to think of it, before we came here,
Piccolo mentioned
the Demon Realm's Dragon Balls.
Are they really here too?
Yes. Of course.
Whoa, seriously?!
You could say the Demon Realm
Dragon Balls are the originals.
Wow! How do you find 'em here?
Find them?
There's no need to find them.
Everyone knows where they are.
You know? What do you mean?
There are three Demon Worlds
in the Demon Realm.
This is the Third Demon World.
Each Demon World has a Dragon Ball
in a specific location.
Warriors called Tamagami guard them.
Tamagami?
So you need to steal the Balls
from the Tamagami?
Yes. But that's no easy feat.
The Tamagami are incredibly strong.
They're really that strong?
Yes.
You must fight and defeat them
to obtain the Balls.
I take it one must do that three times
to have a wish granted.
Is that correct?
Exactly.
So you only need to gather
three Dragon Balls here?
That sounds super duper fun!
Wow! I wanna gather the Dragon Balls!
You can't.
As far as I know, no one has ever gathered
all three and had a wish granted.
That just makes me wanna try it more!
You can't, Goku-san.
Rescuing Dende-san comes first.
Hey, is the Tamagami far from here?
Remember the Warp-sama where we arrived?
It's in the opposite direction.
The opposite?! That's too far.
Maybe so, but…
If we get the Dragon Balls and
make a wish while goin' to rescue Dende,
we can become grownups again!
That's true, but…
I see.
That might be worth pursuing.
Now you're agreeing with this?
What happens if that Dende fellow
is killed or you can't find him?
If you use the Demon Realm Dragon Balls
to make a wish, you can rescue Dende,
and you can return to normal
with the Earth Dragon Balls.
Right?! Let's do it!
Woo-hoo!
Very well.
Hooray!
I can see the next town!
We can finally get somethin' to drink!
Plus I'm hungry!
It would be nice to rest.
Oh! Water!
Oh, Goku-san!
Is the water here safe to drink?
I think so.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Tch! It's the Military Police.
Military Police?
The Great Demon King's private army.
We will now begin gathering
this year's offerings!
Silence!
As you well know,
with King Dabra's death, Gomah-sama has become the Great Demon King as of a few days ago!
King Gomah feels that the demand for
offerings has been too lenient.
As such, starting now…
offerings will be three gold coins!
Three coins?!
That's impossible!
Anyone who fails to pay will forfeit
three years of their lives per coin!
So anyone who can't pay a single coin
will pay nine years! Got it?!
Th-That's too cruel!
I'm sure you're aware that
there's no point in running!
With the Magic Collars on
your necks, we will find you!
They got me!
Fleeing will cost you another
ten years! Is that clear?!
That's horrible. They're out of control.
Can you believe those guys?
Come on! Cough them up!
Good! Next!
Wait. This isn't enough.
This is all that I have.
Take him.
Come on!
Tch. Can you believe these guys?
Should I beat the heck outta them?
Don't. It'll cause more trouble.
Please! I'll pay next time! Forgive me!
If I lose nine years
of my life I might die!
Not happening!
Do it!
Hey! Stop picking on an old man!
Why you…! Why you…!
Hey! Stop struggling, old man!
Hey!
That's enough, you creeps.
Who the hell are you?
Ta-da! Taste this hand-made Wasabi Bomb!
Take this!
Whoops!
G-Get them!
- Get back here!
- Why you…!
Let go! You big brute!
- Move!
- Out of the way!
Enough! Stop struggling!
You little bastard!
Get outta here!
Hey!
Who the hell are you?!
Whoops, I went too far.
Y-You! Who are you?!
This way, quickly!
Hurry!
- Hey!
- Stop!
And now you've become a fugitive.
Don't blame me.
I couldn't let them do that.
Good point.
Who are you?!
Oh! It's you!
Hold out your palms to the wide-open sky
Te no hira wo oozora ni
Hold them up high in this moment
Kazashite ima
and make a miracle happen
Okose kiseki wo
Just like that bird, we fly
Ano tori no you ni We fly
While gathering up pieces of hope
Kibou no kakera wo atsumenagara
There's no giving up!
Akiramenai kore kurai!
Just gotta go as far as we can
Ikeru toko made itte miru dake
With our friends by our side
Nakama to nara
Run run run run
Over that mountain we go
Ano yama wo koete
I can hear your voice sounding always
Kikoeru yo kimi no koe ga itsumo
"We're not alone, you know"
"Hitori janai darou"
PANSY